

I'm a freelance visual/UX designer and sometimes front-end developer trying to figure out what's next for me. I am interested in making products that improve people's lives and make them smile. I believe in living what you love, and that includes my work. I would love to get my creative juices flowing and collaboratively work with a design team focusing on great experiences.

ANGELLOV.ES

y @ANGELK

■ ANGEL.KITTIYACHAVALIT@GMAIL.COM

SKILLS

Visual design, UI/UX design, illustration, lettering, Adobe Suite, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, photography, making greeting cards, laughing, and making name tags.

EDUCATION

University of California, Berkeley B.A., Economics *August 2008*

AWARDS

GSMA mWomen Design Challenge Grand Prize Winner

February 2013

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Designer

Design & Happiness Studio, San Francisco, CA October 2009–Present

I do graphic design, illustration, lettering, web and mobile design, UX/UI design, and front-end development for various clients.

Interaction Designer

AltSchool, San Francisco, CA June 2014–August 2014

I worked closely with the product manager, engineers, and UX researchers designing and implementing the teacher workflow. I designed wireframes, performed user testing, designed high fidelity mockups, and helped with implementation.

Designer in Residence

Code for America, San Francisco, CA *December 2012–December 2013*

I designed marketing material for all of the 5 programs of Code for America as well as mentored fellows with their projects.

2012 Fellow

Code for America, San Francisco, CA *January 2012–November 2012*

I worked for the city of Chicago, where I was in charge of designing and performing the user testing of web applications that dealt with 311 data. I also helped with front-end development. In addition to Chicago, I also helped design Honolulu Answers and other material for Code for America as a whole that included a newsletter template, the initial site for their Accelerator program, and an icon known as the flag tag.

User Experience Designer

Shop It To Me, San Francisco, CA January 2010–December 2011

As the sole designer, I designed new products, experiments, and various marketing collateral from web to print that impacted over 3 million users. Additionally, I started their user testing program. I conducted several user testing sessions. I worked closely with the CEO and Product Manager to take action from users' feedback. Besides user testing, I implemented a number of other design methods including developing personas, paper prototyping, wireframing, interactive brainstorming as well as creating several iterations of mockups in an agile environment.